Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series III. Project Records
  - Project files
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico - Max Brown Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico - Max Brown Reports, 1968-1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, 1968-1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico - Publicity, 1961-1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, November - December, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, April-October, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, November - December, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, August - October, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, May - July 1965 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, January - April, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, January - May, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico - Project 1 F, May-August, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico - Staples Progress, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel Golf Course, Puerto Rico, 1956-1961 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Duke University, Durham, NC - Research Center Ideas, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - US Open (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Weller, Frank (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - American Junior Golf Association (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Employee Information Reports (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Robert Trent Jones Memorial Scholarship Fund (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Fox Hollow Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Change Orders, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Fox Hollow Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Schedules, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Fox Hollow Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Grassing, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Fox Hollow Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Contracts, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Fox Hollow Golf Club, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Daily Log, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Daily Log, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Material, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Rebills, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Grassing, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL -Irrigation, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL - Invoices, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Greenville Golf Course, Greenville, AL - Contracts, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Orange Beach, AL - Irrigation, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Playa Grande Golf Course, Dominican Republic -Billings and Contract, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Playa Grande Golf Course, Dominican Republic -Memos and Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Playa Grande Golf Course, Dominican Republic -Barefield's Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Adare Manor, Ireland (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Robert Trent Jones International Golf Club, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Vidauban, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Wells College, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Wigwam Resort, Litchfield Park, AZ, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Vancouver, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Marion County Comprehensive Plan, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Aerial Photograph (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence golf courses (Box 37)
    - Activity reports, Adrian Argyle Cooper, 1990-1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Lindau (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Specs (Beard), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Agadir correspondence, contracts, invoices, 1985-1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Agadir seed, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Agadir general correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Agadir labour/machinery, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Les Jardins de la palmieraie Maintenance equipment and building information (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Les Jardins de la palmieraie Irrigation, letters, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - Courses and Aerial (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Rivera Golf Club, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Golf de Sperone, Corsica - Specs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Golf PR International (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Golf Club of Geneva, Switzerland, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Pevero Golf Club, Costa Smeralda, Sardegna (Italy), 1969-1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Les Jardins de la Palmeraie, Marrakech, Morocco, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Les Jardins de la Palmeraie, Marrakech, Morocco, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Les Jardins de la Palmeraie, Marrakech, Morocco (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Les Jardins de la Palmeraie, Marrakech, Morocco - Expense Report, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Sotogrande, Guadiro, Spain, 1971-1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Drafting Details (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Brochures (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Courses for remodeling: Burning Tree, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Courses for remodeling: Columbia CC, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Courses for remodeling: Dunes, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Courses for remodeling: Greenville Country Club, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Courses for remodeling: Old Warson Country Club, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Courses for remodeling: Sugar creek, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Inactive Files: Frasco Enterprises agreement, Sugarbush Golf Course, Celebrity, Great Gorge, Point O'woods, Tanglewood, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Westside Country Club agreement, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Rancho design agreement, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Rancho SCGA, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Rancho clippings, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Metadonk National Golf Club agreements, billings, correspondence, miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Lely Development Corporation agreements, billings, correspondence, miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Meeting notes (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Patino Properties, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Vidauban expenses, 1983-1989 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - File folder contents, miscellaneous expense information (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Investments, 1974-1989 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Vidauban billings, 1972-1981 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous expenses, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Merrill Lynch (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous documents (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Niall Fraser (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Red Hoffman Speech, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Medicare explanations (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Aerial Photos correspondence (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Cornell University documents, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon, Cornell University document and Feasibility Study, 1991-1996 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Samuel Dupont, Hexton Farms (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Montclair Golf Club, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Insurance Bids (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Spyglass Hill, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - NY State Tax File [RESTRICTED] (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Somers expenses, audits, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Pilgrim's Harbor Country Club, Wallingford, CT, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico Hills Golf Course, Tarrytown, NY, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills Golf Course, Tarrytown, NY - Max Brown's Reports, 1969-1974 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills Golf Course, Tarrytown, NY - Lysander New Community Golf Course, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Ponte Verde Club, Ponte Verde Beach, FL - Publicity, 1967-1975 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Ponte Verde Club, Ponte Verde Beach, FL, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Ponte Verde Club, Ponte Verde Beach, FL, 1949-1964 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Ponte Verde Club, Ponte Verde Beach, FL, 1949-1963 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Portland Golf Club, Portland, OR, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1977-1981 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1969-1974 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda - Publicity, 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Puerto De Hierro Golf Club, Dominican Republic, 1979-1984 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Radisson Golf Course, Baldwinsville, NY, 1975-1977 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Radisson Golf Course, Baldwinsville, NY - Radisson Development Office, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Radisson Golf Course, Baldwinsville, NY - Radisson Development Office, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Radisson Golf Course, Baldwinsville, NY - Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Vidauban Corporate Structure, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Fuente Del Berro, Seville, Spain - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Madeira, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Breckenridge Eureka Associates, 1985-1996 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Breckenridge Eureka Associates - Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Breckenridge Eureka Associates - Design Contracts Drafts, 1987-1990 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Golf Developments, Inc., 1985-1992 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Corporate Income Tax Return [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - K-1 Financial Report [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. -Agreement with Landlords, Inc., 1966 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Lawsuit Mueller, William D. et al [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Bank Account Information [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Notes, 1974-1991 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Executed Documents, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Partial Deed of Release, 1985-1991 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Master Agreement, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. - Certificate of Incorporation, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Somers golf course correspondence/memo, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - KCS/forms. Application for progress payment, affidavit and unconditional waiver (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Changes to construction agreement, Anglebrook golf club, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Subcontract agreement, Anglebrook golf club, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Subcontract agreement draft, anglebrook golf club, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Somers golf course DEIS public hearing, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Somers golf course architectural material, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Somers golf course executed design contract, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Celtic Manor design billings and payment, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Celtic inns drafts (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Celtic inns correspondence and memos, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Celtic manor executed design/construction, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Celtic manor weekly reports (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Playa grande correspondence, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Celtic manor Tony Roberts, Matthews, Jarvis and Associates, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Celtic Manor bills, 3rd course, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Ipswich clubs corporate documents, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Vidauban (8), 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Vidauban (9), 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Vidauban (11), 1982-1983 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Vidauban (12), 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Vidauban (13), 1972-1981 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Vidauban (14), 1980 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Vidauban (15), 1974-1981 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Vidauban (16), 1976-1990 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Vidauban - Photographs (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Vidauban - Zac du Bois de Bouis, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Vidauban - Bois de Bouis, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Falcon's Lair, Mesquite, TX, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Manassas Golf Club - Robert Trent Jones Golf Club, Manassas, VA, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Metrowest Golf Course, Orlando, FL - Par 3, Debra Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Playa Grande, Santa Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Playa Grande, Santa Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Playa Grande, Santa Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Playa Grande, Santa Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Playa Grande, Santa Domingo, Dominican Republic, 1962-1993 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Point O'Woods Golf Course and Country Club, Benton Harbor, MI, 1981-1994 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Port Royal Golf Course, Bermuda, 1987-1995 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Punta Cana, Dominican Republic, 1988-1995 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Rancho California - Walker Basin, Temecula, CA, 1989-1991 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Rio Rico, AZ - Avatar, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Siwanoy Country Club, Bronxville, NY, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Sotogrande (3), Spain, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - South Glen Estates, Kinnelon, NJ, 1963-1993 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Vidauban (6), 1976-1979 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Vidauban (10), 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Wales - The Celtic Manor Golf Course - Short Course and Putting, 1993-1995 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Wales - The Celtic Manor Golf Course - Philip York, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Wales - The Celtic Manor Golf Course (1), 1983 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Wales - The Celtic Manor Golf Course (2), 1990-1993 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Leads - Potential Golf Course Constriction, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Leads - Prospect - Gaston Raoul - Coolies's rift Resort and Golf Course, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - US Golf Association, 1991-1994 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - PGA Tour player/manager list, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Water Reuse evaluation, 1988-1990 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Duke University RTJ room, 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - St Andrews, Scotland- Kingask Estate, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Sketches, new designs, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Proposals, miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Coral Ridge Country Club, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Publicity: interviews, endorsing book, etc., 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Breakwater Towers, Fort Lauderdale FL, 1991-1996 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Adare Manor, Ireland, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: layouts, holes, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - American Golfers' Club, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Adache, Dan. Architect, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Leonard and Morrison attorneys, 1990-1992 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Pine Valley Golf Club, 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Robert Trent Jones Inc. Work papers, notes, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Morgan Guarantee Co., 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Oak Hill Country Club, Rochester, NY, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Photographs miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Pinehurst, NC, 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous faxes (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Alabama golf trail (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Golf Course Superintendents Association, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Yale Club of NYC, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Lago Mar receipts, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Trial Balances, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Xerox Maintenance agreement, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Florida Golf balances, receipts, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Mashantucket Pequot expenses, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Phillip York, Celtic Manor invoice, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Disposal of Montclair House, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Legal bills [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - RTJ Golf ventures celebration, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - RTJ interim report, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Golf Group brochure (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - RTJ Ventures Edina Golf Club, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - RTJ Ventures Fox Hollow Retainage, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - RTJ Ventures: Florence, Italy, Marzi, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - RTJ Ventures: Cartle Harbor Lead, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - RTJ Ventures: Leads checklist (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - RTJ Ventures: Press releases, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Project Financing North American Resort and Golf Inc., 1997 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Carolina Trace Country Club brochure (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Royal and Ancient Golf Club rules (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Standard coffee service, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - The USGA membership dues, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - National Golf foundation, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - American express documents, 1997-1999 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Visa Card, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Value Press stationary documents (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Vat taxes, Ireland [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Grand opening Coldra Woods expenses, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Arcola receipts, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Celtic Manor draft, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Fairview invoice, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - CYD Japan statements, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Celebration Golf Course, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - MN workers' compensation notice, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Billings to Golf Group, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Medinah report, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Paducah invoice, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - RTJ Golf ventures Aberdeen proposal, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Golf Group press releases, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Fenwich and West Statements, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - RTJ Florida: NJ taxes [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - CYD Letters, Greenberg Golf Course, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Meridian Vat Reclaim Application, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - A and L Goodbody- FGC Irish taxes [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - Poe and Brown, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 49)
    - Bill Naiditch observations, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 50)
    - RTJ Ventures press articles, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 51)
    - RTJ Golf Club invoices, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 52)
    - RTJ Course List, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 53)
    - Benedetti file, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - Gibralter bank, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - Thomas Guidicelli file, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - Groppi invoices, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Prospect Gradens Dissolution, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Golf construction, Italy. SRL, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 59)
    - Foreign Corporation structure and legal coding (Box 79, Folder 60)
    - RTJ Companies cash flow and budget, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Employment Contracts, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Drafts, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Correspondence and Memos, 1990-1993 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Costs, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Sotogrande, Spain - Contract, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Golf de Sperone, Corsica - Contract, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Golf de Sperone, Corsica - Correspondence and Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Riviera Golf Club, France, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Riviera Golf Club, France - Correspondence and Memos, 1990-1995 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Promotional, Articles and Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Hold, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Billings and Payments, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Environmental Assessment, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Drafts of Contracts, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Background Information (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Executed Design Agreement, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Mauna Kea Golf Course, South Kohala, HI - Correspondence and Memos, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Information Sheets (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Design Proposals/Requests - Affirmative, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Design Proposals/Requests - Negative, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Alabama (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Palomino Golf and Country Club, Scottsdale, AZ, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Arizona, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - California, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Connecticut, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - Mashanticket Pequot Tribe, CT, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 28)
    - Delaware, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 29)
    - Florida, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 30)
    - St. Augustine, FL, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 31)
    - Georgia, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 32)
    - Illinois, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 33)
    - Maryland, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 34)
    - Michigan, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 35)
    - Nevada, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 36)
    - New Jersey, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 37)
    - Liberty State Park, NJ, 1989-1991 (Box 87, Folder 38)
    - New York, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 39)
    - New York Institute of Technology, Old Westbury, NY, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 40)
    - North Carolina, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 41)
    - Oregon, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 42)
    - Pennsylvania, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 43)
    - South Carolina, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 44)
    - Tennessee, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 45)
    - Texas, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 46)
    - Virginia, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 47)
    - Washington State, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 48)
    - West Virginia, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 49)
    - Wisconsin, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 50)
    - Orlando and the Cayman Islands (Box 87, Folder 51)
    - John Harvey, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 52)
    - Design Billing, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 53)
    - Licenses, 1985-1989 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Phillips and Jordan (P&J) Rebill, 1991-1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Phillips and Jordan, 1991-1993 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Rents and Per Diems, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Auto CAD Surveying, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Amur, fish as biological weed control, 1975-1988 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Aronimink Golf Club, Newtown Square, PA - Billings, 1987-1990 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Aronimink Golf Club, Newtown Square, PA (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Aruba Golf Course - Michael Garfield and Herman Nahar, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Ballybunion, Ireland, 1986-1990 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Barbados, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Bellerive Country Club, St. Louis MO, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Barbuda, Island of (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Barbuda, Island of (Near Antiqua), 1988 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Burning Tree Country Club, Bethesda, MD (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Celebrity Country Club, Tulsa, OK, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - City of Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Sewage Spill, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club, Barnardston, MA, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Crumpin-Fox Club, Barnardston, MA, 1988-1990 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Croton-on-Hudson, NY, Prickly Pear Hill Golf Course, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Deerwood Pointe Inc., Roanoke, VA, 1989-1991 (Box 89, Folder 22)